nirandfar.com 2016-03-20

# Privacy Policy - Nir Eyal

### Privacy Policy

Please read this privacy policy carefully. By accessing or using our website, you acknowledge that you have read, understand, and agree to be bound to all the terms of this Privacy Policy and our website Terms of Use. If you do not wish to agree to these terms, please refrain from using the Site.

_Amazon Affiliate:_

NirandFar is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to amazon.com.

_Collection of Information:_

Personal Information that You Provide – When you subscribe to the NirandFar newsletter, we ask you for personal information (such as your name and email address).

Cookies – When you visit the NirandFar website, we may send one or more cookies – a small file containing a string of characters – to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service by storing user preferences and tracking user trends. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features and services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled. In addition, as you browse the NirandFar website, advertising cookies will be placed on your computer so that we can understand what you are interested in. Our display advertising partner, [AdRoll](https://app.adroll.com/), then enables us to present you with retargeting advertising on other sites based on your previous interaction with NirandFar. The techniques our partners employ do not collect personal information such as your name, email address, postal address or telephone number. You can visit this [page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) to opt out of AdRoll and their partners’ targeted advertising.

User communications – When you send email or other communication to NirandFar, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services.

_Use and Disclosure of Information_

In general, Personal Information you submit to us is used by us to provide you access to the NirandFar website and to offer you additional information, opportunities, and promotions from us, our partners or our advertisers. We may provide your Personal Information to third-party service providers who work on behalf of or with us to provide some of the services and features of NirandFar and to help us communicate with you.

Additionally, we may create Anonymous Information records from Personal Information by excluding information (such as your name) that would otherwise make the Anonymous Information personally identifiable to you. This Privacy Policy does not limit our use or disclosure of any Anonymous Information in any way, and we reserve the right to use and disclose Anonymous Information to our partners, advertisers and other third parties in our discretion.

In the event we go through a business transition such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of our assets, your Personal Information may be among the assets transferred. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur and are permitted by this Privacy Policy, and that any acquirer of ours or that acquirer’s assets may continue to process your Personal Information as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

We may disclose your Personal Information if we believe in good faith that such disclosure is necessary to (a) comply with relevant laws or to respond to subpoenas or warrants served on us; or (b) to protect and defend our rights or property, you, or third parties. You hereby consent to us sharing your Personal Information under the circumstances described herein.

_Security_

We are committed to protecting the security of your Personal Information. We use a variety of industry-standard security technologies and procedures to help protect your Personal Information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. Even though we have taken significant steps to protect your Personal Information, no company, including us, can fully eliminate security risks associated with Personal Information.

_Additional Policy Information_

Your Choices Regarding Your Personal Information – We offer you choices regarding the collection, use, and sharing of your Personal Information. You have a right at any time to stop us from contacting you for marketing purposes. When you receive promotional communications from us, you may indicate a preference to stop receiving further promotional communications from us and you will have the opportunity to “opt-out” by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in the promotional e-mail you receive or by [contacting us directly](mailto:nir@nireyal.com?Subject=Privacy%20Policy%20Inquiry)

_Changes to this Policy_

Please note that the NirandFar Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will post any changes to this Policy on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of Policy changes).

If you have any additional questions about our Privacy Policy, please feel free to send us an [email](mailto:nir@nireyal.com?Subject=Privacy%20Policy%20Inquiry).
